Federal Art Project, Photographic Division
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Subject Files, 1935-1942, Series 2:; (Boxes 25-31; 2.8 linear feet)
  - Building Exteriors, circa 1936-circa 1942, (R 1179: 257-386) (Box 25 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Buildings with FAP Artwork, circa 1936-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Changing New York by Berenice Abbott, circa 1935-circa 1939 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Children, circa 1935-circa 1941, (R 1175: 579-807) (Box 25 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Children, 1935-1937, (R 1175: 579-807) (Box 25 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Children, 1938-1939, (R 1175: 579-807) (Box 25 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Civilian Conservation Corps Camps Training School, circa 1936-circa 1942, (R 1179: 130-158) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Educational Exhibitions (Box 26 (hol))
    - Chronic Disease, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R 1177: 121-141) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 2)
    - Visual Aid Objects for Defense, circa 1937-circa 1939 (Box 26 (hol), Folder 3)
    - Why Plan Our City?, circa 1939, (R 1177: 142-160) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Lectures and Symposiums, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 26 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Metal Work-American, circa 1936-1942, (R 1179: 159-172) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Models, Interior, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R 1179: 173-191) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Models, Miscellaneous, circa 1937-circa 1942, (R 1179: 202-256) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Models, Naval and Military, 1941, (R 1179: 192-201) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 9)
  - New York City FAP Exhibitions, (R 1176: 178-938, R 1177: 1-34) (Box 26 (hol))
    - Art Exhibitions, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 26 (hol), Folder 10)
    - Art Exhibitions, 1935-1937 (Box 26 (hol), Folder 11)
    - Art Exhibitions, 1937, (2 folders) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 12-13)
      includes photos with Holger Cahill and others
    - Art Exhibitions, 1938, (4 folders) (Box 26 (hol), Folder 14-17)
    - Art Exhibitions, 1939-1941 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 1)
    - Childrens' Exhibitions, (R 1175: 809-1103, R 1176: 1-26) (Box 27 (hol))
      - Exhibitions, circa 1936-circa 1941 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 2)
      - Exhibitions, 1935-1937 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 3)
      - Exhibitions, 1938 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 4)
      - Exhibitions, 1938-1939 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 5)
      - Exhibitions, 1939-1941 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 6)
    - Childrens' Festival, Central Park, 1938, (2 folders; R 1176: 27-177) (Box 27 (hol), Folder 7-8)
    - Harlem Art Center Exhibitions, circa 1939, (R 1177: 35-51) (Box 27 (hol), Folder 9)
      (includes photos with William H. Johnson, Jacob Lawrence, Augusta Savage, and possibly Gwendolyn Knight)
    - Students with Disabilities/Diseases, Exhibitions, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R 1177: 52-119) (Box 27 (hol), Folder 10)
  - New York City Federal Art Project Branches (Box 27 (hol))
    - Design Laboratory, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R 1177: 499-563) (Box 27 (hol), Folder 11)
    - Easel Division, 1937, 1940 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 12)
    - Graphic Arts Division, 1937 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 13)
    - Home Design Workshops, 1938-1941, (R 1177: 626-643) (Box 27 (hol), Folder 14)
    - Motion Picture Production Unit, 1938-1940, (R 1177: 626-643) (Box 27 (hol), Folder 15)
    - Photographic Division, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R 1177: 185-234 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 16)
    - Photographic Division, Transcript of Signal Corps Photographic Center Dedication, 1942 (Box 27 (hol), Folder 17)
    - Poster Division, circa 1936-circa 1942, (2 folders; R 1177: 235-498) (Box 28 (hol), Folder 1-2)
    - Poster Division, 1935-1938, (R 1177: 235-498) (Box 28 (hol), Folder 3)
    - Poster Division, 1939-1942, (R 1177: 235-498) (Box 28 (hol), Folder 4)
    - Scenic Design and Model Making, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R 1177: 564-628) (Box 28 (hol), Folder 5)
    - Seamen's Institute, circa 1935-circa 1940, (R 1177: 644-671) (Box 28 (hol), Folder 6)
  - New York City Free Art Classes, (R 1174: 264-987, R 1175: 1-578) (Box 28 (hol))
    - Children at Work, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 28 (hol), Folder 7)
    - Children at Work, 1935-1936 (Box 28 (hol), Folder 8)
    - Children at Work, 1937, (2 folders) (Box 28 (hol), Folder 9-10)
    - Children at Work, 1938-1941 (Box 28 (hol), Folder 11)
      (includes photo of Louise Jefferson)
    - Childrens' Art (Box 28 (hol))
      - Paintings, Murals, Lithographs, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 28 (hol), Folder 12)
      - Paintings, Murals, Lithographs, 1935-1936 (Box 28 (hol), Folder 13)
      - Paintings, Murals, Lithographs, 1937, (2 folders) (Box 29 (hol), Folder 1-2)
      - Paintings, Murals, Lithographs, 1938, (2 folders) (Box 29 (hol), Folder 3-4)
      - Paintings, Murals, Lithographs, 1939-1940 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 5)
      - Paintings, Murals, Lithographs, 1941 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 6)
      - Sculpture, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 7)
      - Sculpture, 1935-1936 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 8)
      - Sculpture, 1937-1939 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 9)
      - Sculpture, 1940-1941 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 10)
    - Parent Classes, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R 1177: 52-119) (Box 29 (hol), Folder 11)
    - Students at Work, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 12)
    - Students at Work, 1935-1942 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Other WPA Projects, (R 1178: 774-824, R 1179: 1-16) (Box 29 (hol))
    - Federal Music Project, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 14)
    - Federal Theater Project, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 15)
    - Federal Writer's Project, circa 1936-circa 1939 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 16)
    - Objective Teaching Materials Project, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 17)
  - People Involved with FAP, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R 1177: 691-772) (Box 29 (hol), Folder 18)
  - People Involved with FAP, 1934-1945, 1956, (R 1177: 691-772) (Box 29 (hol), Folder 19)
    (includes photos with Gustave Baumann, Holger Cahill, Raymond Johnson, and Eugenie Shonnard)
  - Processes, (R 1178: 149-592) (Box 29 (hol))
    - Etching, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 29 (hol), Folder 20)
    - Fresco, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 1)
    - Lithography, circa 1937-circa 1939 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 2)
    - Photography, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 3)
    - Sculpture, circa 1937-circa 1941, (2 folders) (Box 30 (hol), Folder 4-5)
    - Sewing, circa 1935-1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 6)
    - Silk Screen, circa 1935-circa 1940 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 7)
    - Silk Screen, 1939 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 8)
    - Wood Engraving, circa 1937 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 9)
    - Wood Working, circa 1935-circa 1941 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Special Functions/Occasions, 1937-1941, (R 1178: 706-773) (Box 30 (hol), Folder 11)
    (includes photos of Holger Cahill)
  - Washington State FAP, (R 1177: 775-912, 1178: 1-7) (Box 30 (hol))
    - Art Galleries, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 12)
    - Artwork, Handicrafts, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 13)
    - Artwork, Models, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 14)
    - Artwork, Mosaics, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 15)
    - Artwork, Murals, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 16)
    - Artwork, Paintings and Drawings, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 17)
    - Artwork, Sculpture, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 18)
    - Interiors, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 19)
    - Men at Work, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 21)
    - People, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 22)
      (includes photo of Holger Cahill and probably Dorothy Miller)
  - Workshop Interiors, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 30 (hol), Folder 23)
  - World's Fair Buildings and Installations, circa 1938-circa 1940, (R 1178: 593-670) (Box 31 (hol), Folder 1)
  - World's Fair Health Building, Leo Lance Gymnastics Mural, 1939 (Box 31 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Unidentified/Miscellaneous, (R 1179: 387-end) (Box 31 (hol))
    - People and Places, circa 1935-circa 1942, (3 folders) (Box 31 (hol), Folder 3-5)
    - People and Places, 1937 (Box 31 (hol), Folder 6)
    - People and Places, 1938-1939 (Box 31 (hol), Folder 7)
    - People and Places, 1940-1942 (Box 31 (hol), Folder 8)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1935-circa 1942, (2 folders) (Box 31 (hol), Folder 9-10)
    - Photographs of Artwork, 1936-1942 (Box 31 (hol), Folder 11)